{
    "id": "5e85c625344e4f57a001f528b9dec745",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Half of my friends ……………………… abroad.",
            "description": "When the noun following half of is plural, we use a plural verb.",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "lives"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………… not wake me up when you come in.",
            "description": "Had better is used to give strong advice. ",
            "answers": [
                "have better",
                "better",
                "had better"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s go ……………………… on the weekend.",
            "description": "Go is used with an ing form in a number of common expressions.",
            "answers": [
                "swimming",
                "to swim",
                "swim"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………. I open the window?",
            "description": "Shall is often used to ask for a suggestion or permission. ",
            "answers": [
                "Shall",
                "Will"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I think I ………………….. this bag.",
            "description": "The simple future is commonly used to announce decisions that are made at the moment of speaking.",
            "answers": [
                "will buy",
                "buy",
                "will be buying"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We are …………………….. for a lot of rain.",
            "description": "Expect is not followed by for. ",
            "answers": [
                "expecting",
                "hoping"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you been to Africa ……………………….?",
            "description": "Before can at any time in the past.",
            "answers": [
                "ever",
                "before",
                "ago"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Did you ever visit Barcelona when you …………………….. in Spain?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "lived",
                "were living"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "His movies are wonderful. I have watched every one of ………………………..",
            "description": "We use a plural noun or pronoun after every one of.",
            "answers": [
                "it",
                "them"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We …………………… go to Thailand on holiday.",
            "description": "Always means every time.",
            "answers": [
                "always",
                "ever"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you ………………………. go to Thailand on holiday?",
            "description": "Ever means at any time.",
            "answers": [
                "ever",
                "always"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… I didn’t know anybody at the party, I had a great time.",
            "description": "Even though and though are possible here. Even though is more emphatic that although. ",
            "answers": [
                "Even though",
                "Although",
                "Even if"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}